Hello
Hello friends Welcome to Extra Friends The
Quarter for Discussion is about to start in a few days
and in such a situation it becomes very important to know
when the quarter results of your favorite companies are coming
because
quarter helps us understand how
any company is performing, whether
its group etc. is doing well or
not, based on the quarter we
can decide whether the future is going ahead with any company or whether the
profit is to be tied here,
so you can understand friends
how important its quarters play for any company,
so let's find out
in today's video
how the result of which company will be seen, by the way
I would like to say one thing and there are
many companies whose quarter food
dates we have covered in our previous videos, if
you want, after watching this video you
can also watch all those videos,
you will find the link in the description box below
and yes the quarters of all the companies are about to
come but we have
included the names of selected companies in our videos
which are important and popular too,
for us the first company here is Mind
Tree works in the IT sector. The
company is a very good company and its
quarterly results are going to come on 18th April. Along with this, there is good
news for the shareholders of the company. Here the company is
also thinking of giving deferment. The
next company here is Larsen & Toubro
Infotech Limited, a company of the Entri group. The
company is a very good company and its
quarterly results are going to come on 19th
April. And see here, this company has also
thought about giving land to its shareholders, but I
would like to tell you one thing here that first the deferment will be
discussed in the board meeting on the day the
company's quarterly results are announced. The
board meeting of the company is also held on the same day. So,
in that board meeting, the deferment is first
discussed. If the vote is approved,
then its shareholders will
get the deferment. The next company is Angel
One. It has also declared its quarterly results
here. You can see that
its quarterly results are going to come in
2013. Well, let me tell you one thing here that the
company has declared deferment a few days ago
with shares on Rupee.  It will pay dividend
and its record date is 11th April.
I am saying again that the next April means the
coming Monday. So, according to this, there will be a
dot on Friday, that is, the
last date. You already know that
you have to buy these shares before this date, that is, within this date. If
you want a difference, then
entry is not made in any company to buy a difference.
Entry is made for the long term only after looking at the fundamentals. The
next company is Tata Elxsi. You cannot even imagine
what a great company it is.
In the last one and a half years, it has given
full returns. Its quarterly
result will come in 2015 and at the same time, the
company will also consider the difference. The
next company is Anty Technology
Services Limited. This is another big company
of Anty Group. Its quarterly result
came on 21st April and this company has
thought about giving growth. The
next company is SNC Group's big name Nestle
India. This time its quarterly
result is going to be very important
because due to inflation, the raw
material has declined.  The cost of production has become quite high,
so you may have heard that a few days ago, the same
company is increasing the prices of its products. This is to
avoid inflation. However, if
you are a shareholder, then let me tell you that there is no
need to panic. This
company will not be ruined like this. This is a very
good company. If there is a raw material quarter, the
company will increase the prices of its products. It will
not be paying from its own pocket,
so there is no need to worry. By the way, no
data is showing here.
I work directly on this and
go to the official note on this, in which the
company had approved a change. So
friends, here we are, you can first see the company's official note
here. There is a
meeting of the company on April 11th. In this meeting, the
company will consider the deferral. If the
deferral is approved, then its
shareholders will get the deferral. The
record date for the deferral has been fixed here on April 22nd.
Now, look here,
another meeting has been scheduled by the company's board objectively for
research, that is,
Nestlé's quarter for cars on April 21st.
Someone is coming now. Keep it on the next page here.
HDFC Life, this company has also
declared its quarterly result date.
Here you can see that the
company's quarterly result is going to come on 26th April.
Next company here, see HDFC
AMC is an APPSC group company and
its quarterly result is going to
come on 27th April. Also,
see here, this company will consider giving dividend.
Next company
is Big Magic Life of the auto sector and
its quarterly result is going to come on
27th April. And
see here, Bajaj Auto is going to reward its shareholders with something different.
Next company here is Persistent
Systems, a company of the IT sector and
its quarterly result is going to come on
27th April. Also, this company is going to
please its shareholders by seeing something different.
Next company here is the
giant Bajaj Finserv. This company has declared its quarterly
result date.
Here you can see that the
water phone result of all these companies is going to come on 28th April.
And this company is also
thinking of giving a difference to its shareholders.
Now here, Ultratech Cement, the giant company of the cement sector, let us
see
when its quarter-final result is going to come.
See here, on 29th April,
Ultratech Cement will declare its quarter-final
result and will make
sodium arrangements for its shareholders. So
friends, these were the quarter-final results of some important popular
companies.
As other companies
declare their results, we will make videos on them too. So, that's all for
now. If you have
not subscribed to the channel yet, then
subscribe because
we keep bringing updates related to the share market on this channel. So,
we will meet
in the next video. Till then, goodbye.